var knowledgedata = {
  "total_size": 4,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "World Jump Day celebrated on?",
      "option1": "20 July",
      "option2": "21 July",
      "option3": "22 July",
      "option4": "23 July",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Bali is an Indonesian Island which is a _________ Island.",
      "option1": "Muslim",
      "option2": "Jewish",
      "option3": "Bhuddist",
      "option4": "Hindu",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question":
          "There are only __________ mountains in the world which are over 8000m/26,247ft above sea level.",
      "option1": "20",
      "option2": "15",
      "option3": "18",
      "option4": "14",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question":
          "Top _______ highest mountains in the world are collectively called as ‘The Eight-thousanders’?",
      "option1": "19",
      "option2": "20",
      "option3": "14",
      "option4": "12",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question":
          "Fukushima Daiichi nuclear power plant is located in which country?",
      "option1": "China",
      "option2": "Japan",
      "option3": "Pakistan",
      "option4": "Russia",
      "ans": "b",
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Who is the longest serving ruler of Indonesia?",
      "option1": "General Suharto",
      "option2": "Joko Widodo",
      "option3": "Sukamo",
      "option4": "None",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The height of Manaslu mountain is?",
      "option1": "8163m/27,781ft",
      "option2": "8423m/27,761ft",
      "option3": "8463m/27,766ft",
      "option4": "8167m/26,795ft",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The height of Dhaulagiri mountain is?",
      "option1": "8137m/26,195ft",
      "option2": "8167m/26,715ft",
      "option3": "8127m/26,791ft",
      "option4": "8167m/26,795ft",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Pakistan biggest city is?",
      "option1": "Karachi",
      "option2": "Lahore",
      "option3": "Multan",
      "option4": "Hyderabad",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "USA’s second biggest city is ?",
      "option1": "Seattle",
      "option2": "New York",
      "option3": "Atlanta",
      "option4": "Los Angeles",
      "ans": "d",
    },
  ]
};
